— RACHEL ROSENSTEIN .—

FULL STACK DEVELOPER - STUDENT

CONTACT

239-691-0046
rachelrosenstein1@gmail.com
View My Portfolio
github.com/rachelrosenstein
linkedin.com/in/rachel-rosenstein/

PROFILE

I am a student in the UPENN Coding Bootcamp looking to be placed in an entry level full stack web development position. I have proficiency in the following programs: Java, JavaScript, Node.JS and expertise with HTML and CSS seek to establish a career as the Full Stack Developer. With this variety of skills under my belt and over 7+ years of customer experience I feel I would be a great asset to a web development team.

EDUCATION

University of Pennsylvania

2020 - Present

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp

An intensive 24-week-long bootcamp dedicated to designing and building web applications.

University of Central Florida

Graduated August 2015

Bachelor of Science: Hospitality and Event Management

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JAVASCRIPT
- JQUERY
- BOOTSTRAP
- FIREBASE
- NODE.JS

EXPERIENCE

Towne Park – Account Manager

September 2018 – March 2020

- Ensures the guest service experience is delivered exceptionally and consistently on all shifts
- Assigns and directs work as well as appraise performances
- Tracks financial Management and reporting
- Ensures that controls are in place for schedules, reporting, timekeeping and overtime
- Effectively deal with internal and external guests' questions, and concerns

The Marquette Hotel - Assistant Front Office Manager

February 2017 - September 2018

- Track guest satisfaction surveys and reviews
- Provide support and leadership for entire Front Office team
- Control labor management, reports, room inventory and schedules.

Four Seasons Resort Orlando - Front Desk Agent, Communications Agent

April 2015 – February 2017

- Proficient in Opera, Open Table, Spa Soft, Front Tee, HOTSOS, and client
- Assigns and directs work as well as appraise performances
- Communicate with owners to assess needs and make recommendations